
{"_id":"0ed6301f-39fe-492f-ab9e-0a72b92653a8","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":1.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$1+1=$","Answer":"2"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"17234444-858a-42c4-93fd-4da032f19696","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":1.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$1+2=$","Answer":"3"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"286b8e20-2a21-4c36-9358-d6797662a535","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":1.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$1+3=$","Answer":"4"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"2fdef6d3-31aa-41e8-a722-77f395c81291","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":1.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$2+4=$","Answer":"6"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"5526c195-e339-4a83-8499-99aef99b001e","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":1.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$3+5=$","Answer":"8"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"73f31156-48c6-4134-8277-783c1d123358","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":2.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$6-4=$","Answer":"2"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"9efb2378-8f4c-4553-97d5-fa24b7a983dd","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":2.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$7-1=$","Answer":"6"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"a048b4fe-6661-4c3b-aa77-a0effeed1706","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":2.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$5-2=$","Answer":"3"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"a9e2c283-2e7c-4c9f-be4b-5e64d1348043","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":2.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$9-3=$","Answer":"6"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"9f8277c9-91c2-4bf4-a12b-c9443e8a041f","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":2.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$10-7=$","Answer":"3"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.006Z"}}
{"_id":"f29851a9-0bf7-4e75-ab3f-8f15b2142468","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":3.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$11+16=$","45Answer":"27"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"f9d29fe6-97ab-4a34-9438-658c37fdd232","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":3.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$33+62=$","Answer":"95"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"b78bed48-dfe9-46ab-ada6-2ce3f9d34647","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":3.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$15+17=$","Answer":"32"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"bb9e2a82-92aa-4036-b797-ab148974c5dd","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":3.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$16+29=$","Answer":"45"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"bc137ef0-fe4b-4b83-abb3-3da3e5dde47a","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":3.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$21+31=$","Answer":"52"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"79c3054d-a1a7-4bb0-843b-fdc3f4bcef2d","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":4.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$69-22=$","Answer":"47"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"800777ec-a100-4f5f-bb3a-1b79f3d6fc7c","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":4.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$89-11=$","Answer":"78"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"8c667dab-cacc-4282-9e95-17c11f332875","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":4.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$78-15=$","Answer":"63"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"8cc47b1b-acf7-41a1-88de-9b81af389f06","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":4.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$71-69=$","Answer":"2"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"9b134b08-605e-4945-8800-d4dc00c25163","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":4.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$26-9=$","Answer":"17"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"c19076fa-0e39-40ef-884f-cf535a04fc15","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":5.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$3\\times 5=$","Answer":"15"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"c4cc56ee-1c54-49b0-93f7-c25adda032db","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":5.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$6\\times 9=$","Answer":"54"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"c8a7ab41-1b1f-4a15-b18e-93eee02e2e71","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":5.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$4\\times 9=$","Answer":"36"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"cbcbc58e-1524-4409-a9bb-76e5fef3fe8e","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":5.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$8\\times 7=$","Answer":"56"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"ccb5ce27-9a81-4d36-b909-82be5cde3e02","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":5.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$2\\times 4=$","Answer":"8"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"d203cd9b-795f-453b-9e98-977434a73c37","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":6.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$10\\div 2=$","Answer":"5"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"d82ab513-227a-4d29-951e-a8694011adc3","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":6.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$9\\div 3=$","Answer":"3"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"e25a7a10-bbb0-4d5b-b70a-7569de486dfe","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":6.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$8\\div 4=$","Answer":"2"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"e5b9fd74-58bb-42b8-abfb-95a815dfff59","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":6.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$18\\div 2=$","Answer":"9"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"edba300f-edc3-46c1-91ea-88f46b40e572","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":6.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$45\\div 9=$","Answer":"5"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"eeff173c-b42e-4a36-839e-58eca3b1cf5d","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":7.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$11+(25-13)=$","Answer":"13"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"ef52037a-4714-4e7d-9166-371ba40989cc","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":7.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$16-(4+25)=$","Answer":"-13"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"1bca54b6-c63a-4cb1-8c72-e3ab74134080","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":7.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$76+(12-5)=$","Answer":"83"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"205fb70e-fc7e-4f78-b9ab-f362ecc3a065","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":7.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$(16+25)-22=$","Answer":"19"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"25eed29a-3dd6-4c0d-ab3c-79e1148417ea","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":7.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$(22-11)+12=$","Answer":"23"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"038e2d1c-158d-446d-a3c5-5d0c246d7842","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":8.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$36\\times 9\\div 12=$","Answer":"27"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"0d15fff3-004f-47ad-b50e-aa2f9c003e43","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":8.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$12\\div 2\\times 6=$","Answer":"36"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"42496853-6605-44f2-aa6e-7f1256b104b6","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":8.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$(16+29)\\div 5=$","Answer":"9"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"4eb8dca3-e60c-4504-8dab-0079df9bbe18","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":8.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$(29-17)\\div 2=$","Answer":"6"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"56e626f9-9521-4376-855b-10057ed37603","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":8.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$22-(33+5\\times 6)\\div 7=$","Answer":"11"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"658599c0-f5b2-477d-b85f-96d31c935a9d","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":9.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$1425+1526=$","Answer":"2951"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"6a6c42cf-9e04-43e7-86a2-298bd814f680","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":9.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$6754-1242=$","Answer":"5512"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"78a5cebe-c1d7-45b5-ad38-720a2065ba7a","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":9.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$2352-1141=$","Answer":"1211"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"11148ea3-734c-4ec8-961b-03d6193eca99","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":9.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$1253235-(13523+13)=$","Answer":"1239699"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"1478d386-8123-4df7-b35e-d7b4c3ee5592","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":9.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$12411+1311-13=$","Answer":"13709"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"14d28d82-60d1-4ff5-b45c-4b7ad4f5aa0e","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":10.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$131\\times 787=$","Answer":"103097"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"07146426-450d-4ecb-bda8-1941cc59217e","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":10.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$1024\\div 32=$","Answer":"32"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"0881037a-397b-4506-9699-383eb96986a0","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":10.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$1446\\div 6=$","Answer":"241"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"023b1ad6-8442-413b-8124-c98de9425fdc","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":10.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$1443\\times 32\\div 12=$","Answer":"3848"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"309b47ce-a811-4384-9192-988a02c1744a","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":10.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$20049\\div 163\\times 2=$","Answer":"346"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"339b45f6-74f0-409e-91d2-a105fa784c77","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":11.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$(1231-131)\\times 243=$","Answer":"267300"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"45e28cff-6948-4d00-82ec-3d7991d4915d","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":11.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$(675-121)\\times (233+232)=$","Answer":"257610"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"56d88bf5-f03f-461a-9ce6-2ef18074df54","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":11.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$(1199+306)\\div (12+23)=$","Answer":"43"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"5fcedec2-2899-467a-aa9a-74f6c6fca608","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":11.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$1231\\times 123-42+131\\times 31=$","Answer":"155432"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"7854a374-2a7c-4ad6-acef-5902f7b07f92","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":11.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$131\\times 121\\div (21-10)=$","Answer":"1441"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"c1ea1978-debd-4503-b952-d9de1b820539","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":12.0,"Qnum":1.0,"Question":"$x+7=9    x=$","Answer":"2"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"ccbf75fc-e825-4988-a802-724fbcc71206","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":12.0,"Qnum":2.0,"Question":"$x-2=5    x=$","Answer":"7"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"7f6fd112-e3d3-414d-9313-68a5ee1f3235","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":12.0,"Qnum":3.0,"Question":"$x^{2}+2\\times x+1=0    x=$","Answer":"-1"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"88fdfbbe-17f5-41f9-90a9-8635b2fafb11","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":12.0,"Qnum":4.0,"Question":"$x^{2}-5\\times x+6=0    x=$","Answer":"2;3"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
{"_id":"8b1e1d72-3690-4eac-9ead-e61d963a66b1","_openid":"oWZqL5Vtf5-8zjT1MssrR3Es7sd8","data":{"Cnum":12.0,"Qnum":5.0,"Question":"$x^{2}+6\\times x=7    x=$","Answer":"-7;1"},"time":{"$date":"2019-11-06T15:06:44.000Z"}}
